okay I wanted to give everyone a quick
tour of my garage gym
AKA Breet contr strength and
conditioning or
bcsc here's the air
dine um here I've got a bucket full of a
bunch of random stuff two board manade
hit
belts um got an incline press here
um competition bench press right here
from Elite
Fitness right here is the
scorcher I've got a power rack here in
the corner that isn't being used
um see moving over
here here is a
um dual uh cable
column some pulling blocks and different
bars and handles and stuff all right
this is the bad boy right here this
power rack from Elite Fitness I actually
have the monkey chin bar upside down
because um if I didn't I'd hit my head
on the on the ceiling but here I've got
all sorts of bands and
different chains and belts and things
things and this is a huge platform
here here I've got adjustable bench ax
pad Hampton thick bar pad this what I
use to uh reduce pressure when I do hip
thrust um military press
bench bunch of different dumbbells I
only have up to 100 pounders I wish it
went up to uh like 160s but oh well here
I've got my reverse
hyper
um and then bunch of different gadgets
here AB wheel foam rollers Swiss ball
Sledgehammer
um front squat harness tornado
ball um the stick lacrosse ball okay
here I've got a 45
hyper those are um band Peg
attachments couple of box squat boxes
there here I have a glute ham
raise developer glute ham developer okay
this here is a deadlift lever right
there deadlift bar lever and then
there's a step up attachment that
attaches to the power rack so I can do
step step UPS from any height and then
here I have a lever squat Mach
machine and then behind there is a
safety squat bar and there's a
rackable cambered
bar and a chalk
bin and then here
is an FMS kit so I used to have all this
stuff um spread out in a 1300 ft
facility but now it's all packed in here
into my like 500 squ ft garage so it's
pretty packed in here it's not very
convenient but hopefully I'll move all
my equipment somewhere and it'll be more
spread out in the future anyway that's
uh my garage hope you liked it I'm out